

GENÍS GILAVERT BERLANA

Diluvi nº 7, 2º 2ª, Barcelona 08012

4 93 448 36 23 **609 156 909**

■ anonymousheimer@gmail.com

https://github.com/anonymousHeimerdinger

SUMMARY

Leadership skills, analytic capacity and excellent problem solving skills.

Big potential in mathematics and programming.

Two years in the mathematics degree with mention in computing.

At change of job to computer systems administrator, stopped the carreer and continued expanding knowledge with others programming languages.

Currently, working and studying several courses of Programming and English.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Waiter January 1997 to January 1999 Bar Oasis - Hospitalet de Llobregat January 1998 to January 2004 Football referee Federació Catalana de Futbol - Barcelona **Bellbov** March 2002 to June 2002 Grupo de Hoteles Gargallo - Barcelona October 2004 to October 2004 Collaborator Jornadas Internacionales de fisioterapia - Barcelona **Commercial** November 2004 to January 2005 Publingenios - Barcelona January 2005 to September 2005 **Administrative Assistant** Air France - Tremblay-en-France **Network Operator for telefonica** October 2005 to December 2005 Spark Ibérica - Barcelona Soldier in the specialty of transmissions April 2006 to August 2017

Ministerio de Defensa - Madrid

Teacher of programing of Video Games with POO and Javascript March, 22th 2019 Espai Barcelona - I was invited to give a class of programing of Video Games with the use of POO and Javascript

Computer systems administrator

May 2017 to August 2019

Omega Peripherals - Barcelona

TRAINING

TRAINING	
Federació Catalana de Futbol Camp Barcelona Football referee title: Sports	1998
Institut Eduard Fontserè Hospitalet de Llobregat Baccalaureate title: Technological	2003
Dirección General de Tráfico Barcelona Driving license class B	2003
Spark Ibérica Barcelona Network Operator course: Computing	2005
Acuartelamiento San Fernando Zaragoza IT Essentials course: PC Hardware and Software: Computing	2011
CAMPUS 25 Barcelona University access certificate	2011

Universitat Pompeu Fabra

Barcelona

Decoding Algebra course: Mathematics

Universitat Autónoma de Barcelona

Barcelona
Course 1 of Design and creation of videogames: Videogames programing

Universitat de Barcelona 2017

Barcelona

Two years in the mathematics degree with mention in computing: Pure mathematics

subjects of computing degree:

- o Algorísmica
- Programació II
- Estructura de dades
- o Dissenv de Software
- Projecte Integrat de Software

Commvault 2018

New Jersey
Commvault Technical Sales Professional - CVTSP19

Espai 2018

Barcelona

Higher course of development and implementation of web applications

I designer not finished yet ...

Barcelona

Programing of Video Games with Unreal Engine 4

CEPI-BASE not finished yet ...

Barcelona

Course of Visual C#/C++.NET and SQL

KNOWLEDGES, SKILLS AND APTITUDES

Programming languages

C, C++, C#, R, Java, Mathematica, Powershell, Python, PHP and Javascript

Others languages

HTML5, CSS3, jquery, Linux, ajax and SQL

Languages

Native: Spanish, Catalan

Medium: English (level B1, studying for B2

offical exam)

Work platforms

Netbeans

AndroidStudio

Mathematica

Eclipse

Microsoft Visual Studio

Visual Studio Code

Applications

Videogame: Bubbles math Javascript

2017

competition of web videogames

backup analysis Java

free

Videogame: FlyAway Android

subject "integrated software project"

Multimedia plaver Java

subject "programing II"

Programming projects

Test web PHP

php final exam

Commercial web HTML5 and CSS3

html final exam

Kangaroo service Java

subject "software design'

movies and series service Java

subject "software design"

Other programs C and C++

various subjects

AWARDS AND ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS

university awards

Qualification of Honor's Registration in the subject "Elements de programació"

other awards

Contest of programming a math videogame in Javascript

individual sports

☆ Athletics

- 1º Classified T cross of "Hospitalet de Llobregat"
- 1º Classified T trophy "ROBERTO CABREJAS" in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"
- (3 km) Obtaining the record of the lower time in the institute's history
- 1º Classified T Militar trophy "Trofeo SAN FERNANDO" (5 km) in the army

Between the position 100 and 200 of 60 thousand participants in the race of "El Corte inglés" (about 12,5 km in 41 minutes)

ir Chess

- 1º Classified T tournament in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"
- 1º Classified T League in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"
- 1º Classified T summer tournament in a English school camp

Shot with long weapon

10 Classified **Y** Militar trophy "SAN FERNANDO" in the army

₩ Videogames

1º Classified **?** 2 times at tournament of "Super Smash Bros"

collective sports

Football

- 1º Classified Many trophies of league "LAS PLANAS"
- 1º Classified T Champions league "LAS PLANAS"
- 1º Classified T summer tournament played in zone Pedralbes in barcelona

Volleyball

1º Classified T tournament in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"

™ Videogames

Diamond level playing "League of Legends"

In the 10 best players of the world with the champion Heimerdinger in "League of Legends"

1º Classified T tournament of couples playing at "Pro Evolution Soccer"